{
    "id": "ffae6eef4c4b414d9798eef4f81d4fc7",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Drop And Draw",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5986e09094cc4a70aeb5f9a9cd08df66",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Drop And Draw",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I dropped ............................. my aunt's house yesterday.",
                    "description": "To drop round is to visit without making an arrangement. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "on",
                        "round"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The demand for digital cameras has dropped ............................",
                    "description": "It demand drops off, it becomes less.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "out",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I dropped ..................................... in the middle of the show.",
                    "description": "To drop off is to begin to sleep.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "out",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Profits dropped ................................. during the last quarter.",
                    "description": "Drop off can mean become less.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "back",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Get in. I will drop you ............................... at college.",
                    "description": "To drop somebody off is to take them to a place.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "out",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Aunt Martha would often drop .......................................... on us.",
                    "description": "To drop in on somebody is to visit them informally.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "up",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can drop .................................... whenever you want.",
                    "description": "To drop over is to visit casually.",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "on",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Nights draw ...................................... fast in winter.",
                    "description": "When nights draw in they start earlier.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "out",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He drew ................................. the lecture unnecessarily.",
                    "description": "To draw out a lecture is to make it longer.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "out",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Drivers are required to draw .................................. at the lights.",
                    "description": "To draw up is to halt.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "up",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don't want to get drawn ......................................... this scandal.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "into",
                        "onto"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The protestors drew .................................. when the police approached them.",
                    "description": "To draw back is to move away.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "out",
                        "back"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}